Coming back with a letter from Garond
I intend to finish the second chapter
So far the area seemed pretty peaceful
Not mentioning those orcs
the ones I saw walking near Cavalorn's hut
In the distance there's some character
It's unsettling that I don't see the face of the gentleman
I feel...
Ohhh, man...
I feel his stare on me
eyes red like a flame
I don't know his intentions
What could he want from me?
I'd rather not provoke him
My head is starting to hurt
I keep having hallucinations
Everywhere I see his mask
I feel fear when I look at it
Everytime it's even scarier
Now I'm seeing it again
In the city, on the farm
He keeps staring at me
And follows me around like a partner
but it's still an enemy
I see my own reflection in him
but only black magic
Darkness decorates his robe
I'd rather not follow his tracks
I have enough of this suffering
Why are you turning me into a monster?
As if I had not enough worries
I need to finally learn the truth
take that cursed mask off
I feel his stare on me
eyes red just like a flame
I don't know his intentions
What could he want from me?
I'd rather not provoke him
My head is starting to hurt
I keep having hallucinations
Everywhere I see his mask
I feel fear when I look at it
Everytime its even scarier
Now I'm seeing it again
In the city, or the farm
He keeps staring at me
and follows me just like a partner
but it's still an enemy
Take this cursed mask off
She hides under a robe
Everyone would want such a chick
Additionally, she also likes magic
knows maybe 100 spells
Maybe I can work for her?
I'd like to be a Seeker
and I don't know how I'll explain myself
I want to be only with her
Special thanks for helping create the remix for:
Bogu9821, Mateusz K. Michalski, Hahel, Miltonek, PLKRKNH, Kot
Thanks also to everyone, who helped, but wasn't mentioned here
[The above is a list of patrons/supporters]
Merch: mylubimypalic.pl
I encourage subscribing, liking, commenting and sharing the remix!
One thing is certain - We will meet again
[ENG sub by Gat1Day]