Xardas
Always this Xardas
We have something you cannot take from us
Some in robes
others in rags
There is one enemy -
that cursed necromancer
Xardas
Always this Xardas
Don't let yourself fall for this devil's tricks
I can depart
Teleportation
It will be best, if you disappear from the city
Xardas
Always this Xardas
We have something you cannot take from us
Some in robes
others in rags
There is one enemy -
that cursed necromancer
Xardas
Always this Xardas
Don't let yourself fall to this devils tricks
I can depart
Teleportation
It will be best, if you disappear from the city
At least for some time...
[ENG sub by Gat1Day]